https://www.helimetrex.com.au/privacy-policy/

About Us
This is the privacy policy of HELImetrex Pty Ltd (“HELImetrex”). This privacy policy explains how your personal information will be treated when you deal with us, when you visit www.helimetrex.com.au (“Website”), including but not limited to, viewing pages, making a purchase, commenting on a page, or creating a user account.
HELImetrex respects your privacy and is committed to the protection of it!
What type of information do we collect?
HELImetrex collects information either online, by email, post, face to face, over the phone, or through partners. In most cases, the personal information HELImetrex will collect from you is the personal information required in order to provide services to you, and also for ongoing management and support services. This information may include the following;
Name
Mailing or street address
Email address
Telephone number
Fax number
ABN
Other information may be collected to perform a service or project.
Cookies and Logging
A Cookie is a small text file that our Website may place on your browser as a tool to remember details for your use of our site. As a rule, Cookies are used to make your browsing experience better and enable our Website to provide the service. Cookies are used directly by our Website and by third-party applications to monitor and improve the service provided by the Website. You can opt out of the use of cookies if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or use the opt-out service provided by Google.
When you visit the Website, we log certain information about your device (“device information”), including information about your web browser, IP address, date and time, and information about how you interact with the Website, to help us monitor usage of the Website.
Personal Information and 3rd Parties
There may be occasions where we supply your details to companies we do business with. Your personal information will not be disclosed to a 3rd party other than of the following only when required:
HELImetrex partners
couriers or parties responsible for delivery of your order
anyone employed to provide services for HELImetrex which directly involves the customer
law enforcement agencies as required to do so by law
3rd party service providers who assist us in providing services to you
Our Website may provide interfaces with social media sites such as Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and others. If you choose to “like” or “share” information from our Website through these services, you should review the privacy policy of that service. If you are a member of a social media site, the interfaces may allow the social media site to connect your visits to our sites with other personal information.
The Website may use Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers. Information on how Google uses data when using our Website can be found at https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage. By using our Website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in Google’s Privacy Policy https://policies.google.com/privacy and for the purposes set out above.
HELImetrex uses ServiceM8 for field service management. Some information may be shared with ServiceM8 to facilitate this service with HELImetrex and you. Service8’s Privacy Policy is described at https://www.servicem8.com/au/privacy-policy. ServiceM8 operates in multiple countries and data could be stored in any region ServiceM8 operate in.
If you choose to use PayPal to make purchases through the Website, you will be directed to the PayPal website and provide your payment information directly to PayPal. Some information may be shared between HELImetrex and PayPal to facilitate a transaction, as described in PayPal’s Privacy Policy https://www.paypal.com/au/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full.
Some personal information is stored with HubSpot, a CRM HELImetrex uses. Personal information is stored on HubSpot’s servers is the United States. HubSpot’s Privacy Policy is described at https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy.
Information Security
Your personal information is private and will be treated as such. We take reasonable measures to protect your personal information where applicable. We endeavour to ensure your information is accurate, current and stored in a secure environment.
Our Website is hosted in Australia. Personal information may be transferred, stored, and processed in any country we engage service providers, including the United States. In certain circumstances, courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies, or security authorities in those countries may be entitled to access your personal information.
We do not store credit card information on this site, nor are any payment details such as bank account details.
Your data rights
You have a right to request access to your personal information and to request its correction. We will take reasonably practicable steps to make sure that the personal information we collect is accurate, complete, and up to date.
At your request, we will provide you with a copy of any personal information which we hold about you unless an exception under the Privacy Act 1988 applies. We may charge a reasonable fee for retrieving this information, in which case we will inform you of the fee and seek your agreement to that fee before providing the information.
Acceptance
By logging in and using this site, you consent to the practices described in this privacy policy and accept the use of cookies.
If you have any enquiries regarding this policy, please contact our office by email info(at)helimetrex.com.au or by post PO Box xxx, Everton Park QLD 4053, Australia.
Updates and Notification
HELImetrex Pty Ltd reserves the right to change this policy at any time. There will be no notification that this policy has changed. It is the responsibility of the customer to check the status of our policy each time you provide us with personal information.
European Union – General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
If you are a resident of the European Union for the purposes of the GDPR, then in addition to what is set out above, the following applies to you.
HELImetrex does not actively market or provide services to the European Union, however, we do not block persons from the EU to use the Website or engage with other services HELImetrex may provide if they so choose to do so.
HELImetrex is a data controller and processor for the purposes of the GDPR and by your consenting to this Privacy Policy, HELImetrex is able to process your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Your personal information may be transferred and processed by 3rd parties, in Australia and other countries, as described in this policy.
In providing services to you, HELImetrex may make use of a number of automated processes using your Personal Information and your activity on our site as tracked, in order to provide relevant services to you.
Contact Us
HELImetrex Pty Ltd
Phone : +61 7 3040 2354
Email : info@helimetrex.com.au
Search for:
